icstation.com 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy - ICStation

ICStation.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated when you use or register on ICStation.com. 

**1\. Personal Information Collected By ICStation.com**

"Personal Information" includes your name, address, telephone number, credit or debit card information, e-mail address, date of birth, IP address. ICStation.com users' information that we collecte from our website visitors, registered members and customers . To improve your visiting and online shopping experience at siite, we collect information in following ways: 

**Information You Give to Us:  **We Collect Personal Information that is provided by Site users. It's collected when you establish an account with us, place an order on the Site, participate in a contest, sweepstakes or on-line survey, or when you communicate with any of our departments such as customer service, sales or technical services through the Site, telephone, mail or fax. 

**Web Beacons:  **We (or service providers on our behalf) may collect information from visits to the Site through the use of "Web Beacons." Web Beacons are web page elements which may employ cookie technology that enable us to record data about visits to or transactions made on the Site. This information is sometimes known as "clickstream data." We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics to improve your online experience or our customer service. No Personal Information is collected through the use of Web Beacons on the Site. 

**Cookies:  **Through the use of cookies, we may also collect and analyze the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as your browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase history; confirmation when you open e-mail that we send you; and the URLs which lead you to and around the Site including the date and time. You can generally set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when you have sent a cookie. Software is also available from third parties which will allow you to visit the Site without providing this information. You are welcome to use the Site if you use such software but we will not be able to offer you our personalized services and we will be unable to accept any online orders from you. 

**Orders:  **If you place an order through the Site, you will be required to provide contact, billing, and payment information. 

**eNewsletter Subscription:  **Upon placing an order through the Site, you will automatically begin receiving ICStation.com eNewsletter, based on the Personal Information you have provided, unless you opt-out of receiving such communications

**2\. How does ICStation.com use my information?  **

We use the information in order to improve your online experience, provide services to you and communicate with you about information that you request. We may also use this information to help us target specific offers to you and to tailor our Site to your interests. 

**3\. Security  **

We do not sell or rent to anyone the information you have entrusted to us.   
We do not share your personal information with any companies who want to market their products or services to you.   
We employ 128-bit encryption technology in all areas of the Site which require you to provide your personal or account information, including those areas related to online ordering, order status and contest forms. The Site utilizes industry-standard firewalls and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to allow for the encryption of potentially sensitive Personal Information, such as your name, address and credit card number. 

You should recognize, however, that no computer system is fully secure and that there are inherent risks associated with Internet transactions. To make sure you have the latest security features on your browser, you may want to download the most recent version of your favorite browser, which should have full SSL support. 

**4\. Information Updates  **

If you need to update your personal information, you can log in your account and update it at any time and place. 

**5\. Contact Information  **

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Notice, please e-mail us at orders@icstation.com.
